let quiz = [
    {
        para: "Dasharatha is the King of Ayodhya and has three wives and four sons, Rama, Lakshmana, Bharata and Shatrughana.",
        question: "Which element from the periodc table has 4 as atomic number?",
        option: [
            "Be ",
            "He",
            "O",
            "N",

        ],
        answer: 1,

    },
    {
        para: "When the princes had grown up some, the sage Vishwamitra arrived at Dasharath's court and asked that Rama and Lakshman be lent to him to help him rid his hermitage of the demons that were plaguing the ashram dwellers by defiling their sacrifices with blood and bones. While returning from there they hear of the swayamvar of Sita.",

        question: "Which of the following elements is composed in bones?",
        option: [
            "Na",
            "Ca",
            "K",
            "F",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        para: "Sita, was also known as daughter of the Earth.",

        question: "Which gas s present in the Earth's Atmosphere in the maximum amount?",
        option: [
            "N",
            "O",
            "CO2",
            "H",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Sita, is also the name of an Indian musical instrument",

        question:
            "The strings are made of which element which produce the unique sounds when made vibrations?",
        option: [
            "Copper",
            "Gold",
            "Silver",
            "Steel",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        para: "Dasharatha now wanted to crown Rama as the prince. However, Bharata's mother is Kaikeyi, who resents Rama being the crown prince and sends him to the forests for vanvaas for fourteen years.",

        question:
            " Crowns were made up of which element from the periodic table?",
        option: [
            "Cuprum",
            "Stannum",
            "Aurum",
            "Argentum",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Rama walked over Sitaâ€™s Swayamvar, picked up the bow, strung it, and plucked the bowstring with such a twang that two things happened simultaneously: the twang was heard for miles around, and the force of it broke the bow into two with so great a sound that the king and his courtiers came running from their chambers to see what the commotion was about. And Sita chooses Rama as her var.",

        question: "Which hormone instills bravery and realises fear?",
        option: ["Dopamine", "Oxytocin", "Serotonin", "Histamine"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        para: "Dasharatha now wanted to crown Rama as the prince. However, Bharata's mother is Kaikeyi, who resents Rama being the crown prince and sends him to the forests for vanvaas for fourteen years.",

        question: "Crowns were made up of which element from the periodic table?",
        option: [
            "Cuprum",
            "Stannum",
            "Aurum",
            "Argentum",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "One day Rama and Lakshmana wounded a rakshasas (demon) princess who tried to seduce Rama. But they refused and as she went on to kill Sita in anguish, Lakshmana cut her nose. She flew to Lanka to her brother Ravana for revenge from Rama and Lakshmana.",

        question:
            "What are responsible for healing of wounds and clogging of blood?",
        option: ["Platelets and Carbohydrates", "Calcium and Proteins", "Platelets and Proteins", "Platelets and Calcium"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Ravana sent his uncle Mareecha in the form of a golden deer to attract Sita.",
        question: "Scientific name, Atomic no of Gold is?",
        option: ["Aurum, 79", "Aurum, 83", "Stannum, 96", "Cuprum, 54"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Lakshmana drew a protection border for Sita for her protection from any negative energy/ entity.",
        question: "What are the protection cells in human body?",
        option: ["Nerve Cells", "Red Blood Cells", "Stem Cells", "White Blood Cells"],
        answer: 4,
    },
];